Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Get off.
ترجل.
Get off!
ترجل!
Hurry, get off!
اسرع، انزل!
Move!
يتحرك!
-Move! -Hurry up!
-تحرك! -اسرع!
Move!
يتحرك!
Hurry up!
عجلوا!
[Huang Residence, Western Medicine: Internal and External Medicine]
[مقر هوانغ، الطب الغربي: الطب الباطني والخارجي]
Hurry up!
عجلوا!
[Shadow Detective]
[محقق الظل]
[Episode 11]
[الحلقة 11]
[Shanghai Ren'ai Hospital]
[مستشفى شنغهاي ريناي]
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
Tell me.
أخبرني.
What did you tell Du Linfeng about me?
ماذا قلت لدو لينفينج عني؟
I didn't say anything.
لم اقل شيئا.
I have a good sense of boundaries.
لدي إحساس جيد بالحدود.
The things you told me not to mention—
الأشياء التي طلبت مني عدم ذكرها
I didn't say any of them.
لم اقل اي واحد منهم
I swear.
أقسم.
Like... the fire.
مثل... النار.
You're talking about me?
هل تتحدث عني؟
What about you?
ماذا عنك؟
Where did you go these past few days?
أين ذهبت في الأيام القليلة الماضية؟
Who were you with?
مع من كنت؟
I went back to my old home.
عدت إلى منزلي القديم.
My father's watch was left there.
لقد تركت ساعة والدي هناك.
I went to get it back.
ذهبت لاستعادته.
You didn't go alone, did you?
لم تذهب وحدك، أليس كذلك؟
I went with Guan Cen.
ذهبت مع جوان سين.
Lu Yizhen.
لو ييزين.
I can't believe you.
لا أستطيع أن أصدقك.
You could have gone with anyone else,
كان بإمكانك الذهاب مع أي شخص آخر،
but you insisted on going with him.
ولكنك أصريت على الذهاب معه.
Do you really plan to investigate the old case with him?
هل تخطط فعلاً للتحقيق معه في القضية القديمة؟
Our goals align,
أهدافنا متوافقة،
so it's easier to work together.
لذلك أصبح العمل معًا أسهل.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
But there's clearly someone
ولكن من الواضح أن هناك شخص ما
who can put you at the center
من يستطيع أن يضعك في المركز
and offer you more help.
وأقدم لك المزيد من المساعدة.
Why not consider that?
لماذا لا نأخذ ذلك في الاعتبار؟
Who?
من؟
Du Linfeng.
دو لينفينج.
There's nothing wrong with me.
لا يوجد شيء خاطئ معي.
I think something's wrong with you.
أعتقد أن هناك شيئا خطأ معك.
Do you have some kind of eye disease
هل تعاني من نوع من أمراض العيون؟
that prevents you from seeing any other man
الذي يمنعك من رؤية أي رجل آخر
apart from Guan Cen?
بصرف النظر عن جوان سين؟
Stop talking nonsense.
توقف عن الكلام الهراء.
Alright, let's go get something to eat.
حسنًا، دعنا نذهب للحصول على شيء للأكل.
You're late today.
لقد تأخرت اليوم.
I already have plans.
لدي خطط بالفعل.
With whom?
مع من؟
Aren't you going to say hello?
ألا تريد أن تقول مرحبا؟
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
I'll say hello when you're in a serious relationship.
سأقول لك مرحباً عندما تكون في علاقة جدية.
You go ahead then.
يمكنك المضي قدما إذن.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I...
أنا...
Perfect timing.
توقيت مثالي.
Director Du.
المخرج أنت.
I've finished packing my things.
لقد انتهيت من تعبئة أغراضي.
W-What is this about?
س-ما هذا الموضوع؟
Why are you sitting here?
لماذا تجلس هنا؟
Because I want to sit here.
لأنني أريد الجلوس هنا.
The inspector has his own office.
المفتش لديه مكتبه الخاص.
It's inside.
إنه في الداخل.
You should go sit in there.
ينبغي عليك أن تذهب وتجلس هناك.
The feng shui there is bad.
فنغ شوي هناك سيء.
And I don't want to pack things for Guan Cen.
وأنا لا أريد أن أحزم الأشياء لجوان سين.
Let Dong sit there.
دع دونغ يجلس هناك.
Did you ask for his opinion?
هل طلبت رأيه؟
Dong.
دونغ.
Will you let me sit here?
هل تسمح لي بالجلوس هنا؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Of course I will.
بالطبع سأفعل.
Abusing your power for personal gain.
إساءة استخدام السلطة لتحقيق مكاسب شخصية.
Yes.
نعم.
Is that not allowed?
هل هذا غير مسموح به؟
It's fixed?
هل تم اصلاحه؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
But this kind of thing is everywhere.
لكن هذا النوع من الأشياء موجود في كل مكان.
Next time it breaks, I'll buy you a new one.
في المرة القادمة التي ينكسر فيها، سأشتري لك واحدًا جديدًا.
Inspector?
مفتش؟
You're back.
لقد عدت.
No need to call me Inspector anymore.
لا داعي لأن تناديني بالمفتش بعد الآن.
We're all at the same rank now.
نحن جميعا في نفس المرتبة الآن.
Director Du
المخرج أنت
is the inspector of the Police Station.
هو مفتش مركز الشرطة.
I don't have that many rules.
ليس لدي الكثير من القواعد.
Call him whatever you like.
أطلق عليه ما شئت.
Welcome back, Inspector Guan.
مرحبًا بك مرة أخرى، المفتش جوان.
This is the Police Station.
هذا هو مركز الشرطة.
That's me.
هذا انا.
Okay.
تمام.
An unidentified female body was found near the market.
تم العثور على جثة امرأة مجهولة الهوية بالقرب من السوق.
Prepare to depart.
استعد للمغادرة.
Okay.
تمام.
Yes.
نعم.
Director Du just arrived
لقد وصل المخرج دو للتو
and is facing such a big case.
ويواجه قضية كبيرة.
We haven't worked with him before.
لم نعمل معه من قبل.
Will this work?
هل سيعمل هذا؟
Who knows?
من يعلم؟
Someone knows me.
أحد يعرفني.
If you can get along with him,
إذا كنت تستطيع التعايش معه،
you won't need an adjustment period with me.
لن تحتاج إلى فترة للتكيف معي.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Don't you think the 2 inspectors knew each other long ago?
ألا تعتقد أن المفتشين كانا يعرفان بعضهما البعض منذ فترة طويلة؟
They do seem like they're at odds.
يبدو وكأنهم على خلاف.
I think there have always been rumors like that.
أعتقد أنه كانت هناك دائمًا شائعات مثل هذه.
I'll be on Inspector Guan's side anyway.
سوف أكون في صف المفتش جوان على أية حال.
What's the situation with the deceased?
ما هو وضع المتوفى؟
Our preliminary assessment is
تقييمنا الأولي هو
the deceased was likely stabbed in the organs by a sharp weapon
من المرجح أن يكون المتوفى قد تعرض للطعن في الأعضاء بأداة حادة
and died from excessive blood loss.
وتوفي بسبب فقدان كمية كبيرة من الدم.
No signs of sexual assault before death.
لا توجد علامات اعتداء جنسي قبل الوفاة.
Time of death?
وقت الوفاة؟
Probably around midnight last night.
ربما حوالي منتصف الليل الليلة الماضية.
Look at the necklace on her neck.
أنظر إلى القلادة الموجودة على رقبتها.
It's quite valuable,
إنها ذات قيمة كبيرة
but the killer didn't take it.
ولكن القاتل لم يأخذه.
This means
هذا يعنى
their goal wasn't robbery.
هدفهم لم يكن السرقة.
That's the result of the on-site examination.
هذه نتيجة الفحص في الموقع.
We need to go back for further death investigation.
نحن بحاجة إلى العودة لمزيد من التحقيق في الوفاة.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Okay. Thank you for your hard work, Dr. Ding.
حسناً. شكراً لجهودك، دكتور دينغ.
You're the one working hard, Director Du.
أنت الشخص الذي يعمل بجد، يا مدير دو.
The crime occurred at night yesterday.
وقعت الجريمة ليل أمس.
The chances of eyewitnesses are probably low.
من المرجح أن تكون فرص وجود شهود عيان ضئيلة.
-Let's first investigate...
-دعونا نتحقق أولاً...
Let's follow Director Du's lead.
دعونا نتبع خطى المخرج دو.
Let's first investigate the deceased's background.
دعونا أولاً نتحقق من خلفية المتوفى.
Yes.
نعم.
Look into it.
أنظر إلى الأمر.
Dong, report your findings.
دونغ، أبلغنا عن نتائجك.
Guo Luyao, 23 years old, unemployed,
قوه لوياو، 23 عامًا، عاطل عن العمل،
lived alone in Tanxian Alley.
عاش وحيدًا في زقاق تانكسيان.
The market where she was killed
السوق الذي قُتلت فيه
is only a few hundred meters from her home.
على بعد بضع مئات من الأمتار من منزلها.
The market is empty by noon.
السوق فارغ بحلول الظهر.
And the alley is old,
والزقاق قديم
mostly inhabited by elderly people,
يسكنها في الغالب كبار السن،
so it's difficult to find witnesses.
لذلك من الصعب العثور على شهود.
It wasn't robbery or sexual assault.
لم تكن سرقة أو اعتداء جنسيا.
Could it be the killer had a grudge against Guo Luyao?
هل من الممكن أن القاتل كان لديه ضغينة ضد قوه لوياو؟
Looks like I came at the right time.
يبدو أنني جئت في الوقت المناسب.
I'm sorry, Director Du.
أنا آسف، المخرج دو.
I forgot... you're in this position now.
لقد نسيت... أنت في هذا الوضع الآن.
Dr. Ding, if you can't even remember
دكتور دينغ، إذا كنت لا تستطيع حتى أن تتذكر
such a small matter,
مثل هذه المسألة صغيرة،
the credibility of the Forensic Institute's reports
مصداقية تقارير المعهد الجنائي
drops considerably.
تنخفض بشكل كبير.
People can sit in positions
يمكن للناس الجلوس في أوضاع
that don't belong to them for no reason,
التي لا تنتمي إليهم بدون سبب،
but reports can't.
ولكن التقارير لا تستطيع ذلك.
Well...
حسنًا...
Director Du is here to help us.
المخرج دو هنا لمساعدتنا.
It was found on the deceased's body.
وقد تم العثور عليه على جثة المتوفى.
Laojiumen's chip?
شريحة لاوجيومين؟
Looks like we have another lead.
يبدو أن لدينا دليلا آخر.
Let's split up.
دعونا ننفصل.
Lu Yizhen, go to Laojiumen with me.
لو ييزين، اذهب معي إلى لاوجيومين.
Guan Cen, you go to the victim's home with Dong.
جوان سين، اذهب إلى منزل الضحية مع دونغ.
I... Well...
انا...حسنا...
You what?
انت ماذا؟
Evidence waits for no one. Hurry up and go.
الأدلة لا تنتظر أحدًا. سارع وانطلق.
Meeting adjourned!
تم تأجيل الاجتماع!
Bet!
لكن!
Thank you, Mr. Du.
شكرا لك سيد دو.
Just...
فقط...
this table today?
هذا الجدول اليوم؟
It's not the busy time yet.
ليس الوقت المزدحم بعد.
People will come soon.
الناس سوف يأتون قريبا.
I heard
لقد سمعت
Guo Luyao was here yesterday.
كان Guo Luyao هنا بالأمس.
Yes, she had an argument with Mr. Lyu.
نعم، لقد كان لديها جدال مع السيد ليو.
Mr. Lyu?
السيد ليو؟
Who is Mr. Lyu?
من هو السيد ليو؟
Lyu Zhang, our manager.
ليو تشانغ، مديرنا.
He and Guo Luyao are quite close.
وهو وغوو لوياو قريبان جدًا.
But... I can't really say how close they are.
لكن... لا أستطيع أن أقول حقًا مدى قربهم.
Why did they argue?
لماذا تجادلوا؟
I was seeing them out at the time.
كنت أراهم في ذلك الوقت.
I think I heard something about...
أعتقد أنني سمعت شيئا عن...
bringing in customers and splitting money.
جلب العملاء وتقسيم الأموال.
I didn't hear the details clearly.
لم أسمع التفاصيل بوضوح.
I think it was just drunk talk.
أعتقد أنه كان مجرد حديث في حالة سُكر.
Just drunk talk.
مجرد كلام في حالة سُكر.
Then they left.
ثم غادروا.
Inspector.
مفتش.
I don't think
لا اعتقد
Guo Luyao was the only one living here.
كان قوه لوياو الشخص الوحيد الذي يعيش هنا.
[Men's Health Products]
[Men's Health Products]
I think a man lived here too.
I think a man lived here too.
Chips?
Chips?
Why did she have so many chips?
Why did she have so many chips?
These seem different from the one Ding Eryi found
These seem different from the one Ding Eryi found
this morning.
this morning.
The color is lighter.
The color is lighter.
It's hard to tell if you don't look closely.
It's hard to tell if you don't look closely.
Could they be fake?
Could they be fake?
[To Lyu Zhang, No. 103 Alley, Wangping Street, Sima Road, Shanghai]
[To Lyu Zhang, No. 103 Alley, Wangping Street, Sima Road, Shanghai]
This one seems more genuine.
This one seems more genuine.
[No. 103, Wangping Street, Sima Road]
[No. 103, Wangping Street, Sima Road]
Director Du? Lu Yizhen?
Director Du? Lu Yizhen?
You guys are pretty quick too.
You guys are pretty quick too.
You've already found the suspect's home.
You've already found the suspect's home.
Director Du, any further instructions?
Director Du, any further instructions?
If not, we'll knock.
If not, we'll knock.
Who is it?
Who is it?
Who are you looking for? I think you've got the wrong door.
Who are you looking for? I think you've got the wrong door.
The Police Station.
The Police Station.
Please come with us.
Please come with us.
According to what you said,
According to what you said,
[Interrogation Room]
[Interrogation Room]
you and Guo Luyao were lovers.
you and Guo Luyao were lovers.
She helped you bring in customers to the casino.
She helped you bring in customers to the casino.
You would give her a cut of the money
You would give her a cut of the money
the customers lost.
the customers lost.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Then what were you two arguing about last night?
Then what were you two arguing about last night?
Over money.
Over money.
Bet, bet, bet!
Bet, bet, bet!
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I haven't won a single round yet.
I haven't won a single round yet.
What does this mean?
What does this mean?
You haven't been around my place lately,
You haven't been around my place lately,
so I had to write to tell you.
so I had to write to tell you.
If I don't agree to the 70-30 split,
If I don't agree to the 70-30 split,
you'll snitch to the boss?
you'll snitch to the boss?
Don't put it so harshly.
Don't put it so harshly.
I still have your fake chips.
I still have your fake chips.
You don't want the boss to think
You don't want the boss to think
you're deceiving him with fake chips, right?
you're deceiving him with fake chips, right?
Let me tell you.
Let me tell you.
If anything happens to me,
If anything happens to me,
you won't get off easy either.
you won't get off easy either.
Get off easy?
Get off easy?
With those few bottles of fake medicine you left at my place?
With those few bottles of fake medicine you left at my place?
Manager!
Manager!
You...
أنت...
-Manager! -What is it?
-Manager! -What is it?
Manager,
Manager,
someone's causing trouble.
someone's causing trouble.
You're telling me that?
You're telling me that?
What are you all paid for?
What are you all paid for?
You...
أنت...
Take good care of Mr. Zhang at Table 8.
Take good care of Mr. Zhang at Table 8.
Where did you go after that?
Where did you go after that?
I went to the nightclub.
I went to the nightclub.
With whom?
With whom?
With three of my buddies.
With three of my buddies.
They can all vouch for me.
They can all vouch for me.
So...
لذا...
Lyu Zhang's suspicion is completely cleared?
Lyu Zhang's suspicion is completely cleared?
Yes.
نعم.
I've taken statements from his 3 friends.
I've taken statements from his 3 friends.
And the nightclub's staff members that night
And the nightclub's staff members that night
also remember seeing him.
also remember seeing him.
So we can basically rule him out as a suspect.
So we can basically rule him out as a suspect.
Then this lead is dead again.
Then this lead is dead again.
Alright, that's it for now.
Alright, that's it for now.
We have no new clues for the time being.
We have no new clues for the time being.
We'll continue tomorrow.
We'll continue tomorrow.
Meeting adjourned.
تم رفع الاجتماع.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.
Lu Yizhen.
لو ييزين.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
I'll drive you home.
I'll drive you home.
What?
ماذا؟
You can help me organize the materials on the way.
You can help me organize the materials on the way.
Dong.
دونغ.
I'll drive you home.
I'll drive you home.
Great. I just...
Great. I just...
I... I'd better not trouble you.
I... I'd better not trouble you.
No trouble at all. Come on.
No trouble at all. Come on.
Help!
Help!
Somebody!
Somebody!
Somebody! Help!
Somebody! Help!
Enough! Stop shouting!
Enough! Stop shouting!
Hurry!
Hurry!
The prisoners have escaped! Help!
The prisoners have escaped! Help!
Hurry up!
Hurry up!
The prisoners have escaped!
The prisoners have escaped!
Hurry!
Hurry!
Let's go!
دعنا نذهب!
It's done! Let's go!
It's done! Let's go!
Where is the stuff?
Where is the stuff?
Hurry up!
Hurry up!
What stuff?
What stuff?
Listen to me.
Listen to me.
The stuff is outside.
The stuff is outside.
I'll give it to you after we get out.
I'll give it to you after we get out.
Impossible.
Impossible.
I was put in jail, right?
I was put in jail, right?
That stuff couldn't be brought in. It was inconvenient.
لم يكن من الممكن إدخال تلك الأشياء. لقد كان ذلك غير مريح.
Don't, don't, don't.
لا، لا، لا تفعل.
Listen to me. Listen to me.
استمع لي. استمع لي.
If you kill me,
إذا قتلتني
you'll never get that stuff, right?
لن تحصل على هذه الأشياء أبدًا، أليس كذلك؟
I'll take you there. You can search me!
سآخذك إلى هناك. يمكنك البحث عني!
We're in the same boat.
نحن في نفس القارب.
Now there's no room for you in the boat.
الآن لم يعد هناك مكان لك في القارب.
So,
لذا،
you weren't lying.
لم تكن تكذب.
Where did you hide it?
أين اخفيته؟
Time to leave. If you don't leave now, it'll be too late.
حان وقت الرحيل. إن لم تغادر الآن، فسيكون الوقت قد فات.
What's the situation with the deceased?
ما هو وضع المتوفى؟
Based on the scene,
استنادا إلى المشهد،
the deceased was strangled to death.
تم خنق المتوفى حتى الموت.
No signs of sexual assault before death.
لا توجد علامات اعتداء جنسي قبل الوفاة.
Time of death was approximately
كان وقت الوفاة تقريبًا
between 11 p.m. and 12 p.m. last night.
بين الساعة 11 مساءً و 12 ظهراً الليلة الماضية.
The one who reported it was the maid of this house.
الذي أبلغ عن ذلك هي خادمة هذا البيت.
She went to the countryside yesterday
ذهبت إلى الريف أمس
and just returned this morning.
وعاد للتو هذا الصباح.
She found her lying here after coming back.
لقد وجدتها مستلقية هنا بعد عودتها.
Look, these footprints on the ground
انظروا إلى هذه الآثار على الأرض
must have been left during the crime.
لا بد أن يكون قد تم تركه أثناء الجريمة.
Isn't this just an ordinary murder case?
أليس هذا مجرد قضية قتل عادية؟
Dr. Ding, why did you ask us here
دكتور دينغ، لماذا سألتنا هنا؟
so urgently?
بهذه السرعة؟
An ordinary murder case?
قضية قتل عادية؟
Go take a look over there and you'll understand.
اذهب وألقي نظرة هناك وسوف تفهم.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Have you found anything?
هل وجدت شيئا؟
Other areas are very clean.
المناطق الأخرى نظيفة جداً.
We haven't found
لم نجد
any traces of the killer's entry for now.
هل هناك أي أثر لدخول القاتل حتى الآن؟
There is a safe in the study,
يوجد خزنة في الدراسة
but it remains locked.
لكنها تبقى مغلقة.
Other valuables aren't missing either.
الأشياء الثمينة الأخرى ليست مفقودة أيضًا.
Our preliminary assessment is
تقييمنا الأولي هو
it doesn't look like a robbery-homicide.
لا يبدو الأمر مثل جريمة سرقة أو قتل.
Alright, search more carefully.
حسنًا، ابحث بعناية أكبر.
Okay.
تمام.
Liu Xiaodan, 23 years old,
ليو شياودان، 23 عامًا
just accepted the marriage proposal
لقد قبلت للتو عرض الزواج
from the second young master of Liu's Bank last month.
من السيد الشاب الثاني لبنك ليو الشهر الماضي.
This villa
هذه الفيلا
was a gift from the Liu family to the couple.
كانت هدية من عائلة ليو للزوجين.
They just moved in last month.
لقد انتقلوا للتو في الشهر الماضي.
But there's something special about her.
ولكن هناك شيئا خاصا عنها.
She was a high school classmate of the previous victim.
كانت زميلة للضحية السابقة في المدرسة الثانوية.
Yes.
نعم.
We already saw their photos together
لقد رأينا صورهم معًا بالفعل
in her villa.
في فيلتها.
Liu Xiaodan moved into the villa less than a month ago.
انتقل ليو شياودان إلى الفيلا منذ أقل من شهر.
The maid went back to the countryside for half a day each week.
عادت الخادمة إلى الريف لمدة نصف يوم كل أسبوع.
Combined with the footprints at the scene,
بالإضافة إلى آثار الأقدام في مكان الحادث،
the suspect must have come prepared.
لا بد أن المشتبه به جاء مستعدًا.
This is a photo from the scene.
وهذه صورة من مكان الحادث.
The shoe print is about 25 cm long,
يبلغ طول طبعة الحذاء حوالي 25 سم،
likely men's shoes.
من المحتمل أن تكون أحذية رجالية.
And they aren't straw sandals or leather shoes,
وهم ليسوا صنادل من القش أو أحذية جلدية،
more like rain boots.
أشبه بأحذية المطر.
Additionally,
بالإضافة إلى ذلك،
on the rope
على الحبل
used to strangle Liu Xiaodan,
تستخدم لخنق ليو شياودان،
we found other textile fibers,
لقد وجدنا ألياف نسيجية أخرى،
something like cotton or linen.
شيء مثل القطن أو الكتان.
These clues are still too vague right now.
لا تزال هذه الأدلة غامضة للغاية في الوقت الحالي.
We can't deduce much about the suspect.
لا يمكننا أن نستنتج الكثير عن المشتبه به.
Both victims
كلا الضحيتين
had a lot of valuable belongings on them when they died,
كان لديهم الكثير من الممتلكات الثمينة عندما ماتوا،
but nothing was taken.
ولكن لم يتم أخذ أي شيء.
And there were no signs of sexual assault.
ولم تكن هناك أي علامات على الاعتداء الجنسي.
And they were classmates.
وكانوا زملاء في الدراسة.
It could be a retaliatory killing by someone they knew.
ربما يكون ذلك قتلًا انتقاميًا من قبل شخص يعرفونه.
We can go check their former school.
يمكننا أن نذهب للتحقق من مدرستهم السابقة.
We might find new leads there.
ربما نجد خيوط جديدة هناك.
Okay.
تمام.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Leave it to me and Lu Yizhen.
اترك الأمر لي وللو يي تشن.
Inspector Guan should stay at the police station.
ينبغي على المفتش جوان أن يبقى في مركز الشرطة.
If anything comes up,
إذا حدث أي شيء،
he can handle it immediately.
يمكنه التعامل مع الأمر على الفور.
[Shanghai Girls' High School]
[مدرسة شنغهاي الثانوية للبنات]
It's all here.
كل شيء هنا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Ms. Liang,
السيدة ليانغ،
do you still have any impression of Liu Xiaodan?
هل لا يزال لديك أي انطباع عن ليو شياودان؟
I do have some impressions,
لدي بعض الانطباعات،
bad ones though.
سيئة على الرغم من ذلك.
It seems she caused quite a bit of trouble at school.
يبدو أنها تسببت في الكثير من المتاعب في المدرسة.
They were...
كانت...
the most troublesome students I've ever taught.
الطلاب الأكثر إزعاجا الذين قمت بتدريسهم على الإطلاق.
Many girls were bullied by Liu Xiaodan and her group.
لقد تعرضت العديد من الفتيات للتنمر من قبل ليو شياودان ومجموعتها.
But the school wanted to keep things quiet
لكن المدرسة أرادت إبقاء الأمور هادئة
and covered up many incidents.
وغطت على العديد من الحوادث.
That only emboldened them further.
وهذا فقط شجعهم أكثر.
Ms. Liang,
السيدة ليانغ،
we've already identified 2 members of the small clique.
لقد حددنا بالفعل عضوين من المجموعة الصغيرة.
Can you help us
هل يمكنك مساعدتنا؟
identify the remaining one?
حدد الباقي؟
[Ma Hanqiao]
[ما هانكياو]
According to the school's archives,
وفقا لأرشيف المدرسة،
Liu Xiaodan, Ma Hanqiao, and Guo Luyao
ليو شياودان، وما هانكياو، وغو لوياو
were notorious at school back then.
وكانوا سيئين السمعة في المدرسة في ذلك الوقت.
They bullied many students.
لقد قاموا بتنمر على العديد من الطلاب.
So we can't rule out the possibility
لذلك لا يمكننا استبعاد الاحتمال
that this is revenge from someone they bullied.
أن هذا انتقام من شخص قاموا بتنمره عليه.
The top priority now
الأولوية القصوى الآن
is to quickly identify
هو التعرف بسرعة
which students were bullied
أي الطلاب تعرضوا للتنمر؟
and to find Ma Hanqiao as soon as possible.
والعثور على ما هانكياو في أقرب وقت ممكن.
We don't have much time left.
لم يتبقى لدينا الكثير من الوقت.
By the way, this is the list we got from the school.
بالمناسبة، هذه هي القائمة التي حصلنا عليها من المدرسة.
Distribute them.
توزيعهم.
Prepare to head out.
استعد للخروج.
Okay.
تمام.
Everyone we visited said
كل من قمنا بزيارته قال
they couldn't remember
لم يتمكنوا من التذكر
what happened back then clearly.
ما حدث آنذاك واضح.
However,
لكن،
though the names of those who were bullied
على الرغم من أسماء أولئك الذين تعرضوا للتنمر
they provided are different,
لقد قدموا مختلفين،
one name was mentioned repeatedly.
تم ذكر اسم واحد مرارا وتكرارا.
Everyone without exception mentioned her:
الجميع بلا استثناء ذكروها:
Tao Fan.
تاو فان.
According to them,
وفقا لهم،
they had a class reunion not long ago.
لقد عقدوا اجتماعًا للفصل الدراسي منذ فترة ليست طويلة.
Tao Fan attended it too.
حضر تاو فان أيضًا.
It was the first time she attended a class reunion
لقد كانت المرة الأولى التي تحضر فيها اجتماعًا للفصل الدراسي
since graduation all these years.
منذ التخرج كل هذه السنوات.
But even so,
ولكن مع ذلك،
on that day,
في ذلك اليوم،
she was still publicly humiliated.
لا تزال تتعرض للإذلال العلني.
I heard that after graduation,
سمعت أنه بعد التخرج،
Tao Fan didn't continue her studies.
لم تواصل تاو فان دراستها.
She didn't look for a job either.
ولم تبحث عن عمل أيضًا.
She's just been helping out at her family's restaurant.
لقد كانت تساعد في مطعم عائلتها.
Her family's restaurant is called...
مطعم عائلتها اسمه...
Ruyi Restaurant.
مطعم رويي.
If she works in a restaurant,
إذا كانت تعمل في مطعم،
that matches my information.
التي تتطابق مع معلوماتي.
I ran some tests.
لقد أجريت بعض الاختبارات.
The shoe prints found at Liu Xiaodan's villa
آثار الأحذية التي تم العثور عليها في فيلا ليو شياودان
indeed include oil stains,
وتشمل في الواقع بقع الزيت،
specifically cooking oil.
وخاصة زيت الطهي.
Restaurant?
مطعم؟
I'll go to Ruyi Restaurant and bring Tao Fan back.
سأذهب إلى مطعم رويي وأعيد تاو فان.
Okay.
تمام.
Dong, go with him.
دونغ، اذهب معه.
Director Du,
المخرج أنت،
didn't you ask me to organize the statements?
ولم تطلب مني تنظيم البيانات؟
I...
أنا...
Then... Then I'll... I'll go.
ثم... ثم سأذهب... سأذهب.
I don't have anything else to do anyway.
ليس لدي أي شيء آخر لأفعله على أية حال.
Let's go together. Come on.
دعنا نذهب معًا. هيا.
[Wansheng Street All Are Welcome]
[شارع وانشينغ، الجميع مرحب بهم]
You and Du Linfeng seem quite in sync.
يبدو أنك ودو لينفينج متناغمان تمامًا.
It's just work.
إنه مجرد عمل.
Just like you and Dr. Ding.
تمامًا مثلك ومثل الدكتور دينغ.
Du Linfeng might not see it that way.
ربما لا يرى دو لينفينج الأمر بهذه الطريقة.
I can't control what others think.
لا أستطيع التحكم بما يفكر به الآخرون.
I only need to know what I think.
كل ما أريده هو أن أعرف ما أفكر به.
Thoughts can change.
الأفكار يمكن أن تتغير.
I've never seen anyone
لم أرى أحدا قط
who can resist
من يستطيع المقاومة
Du Linfeng's sugar-coated sweet talk.
حديث دو لينفينج الحلو المغطى بالسكر.
I can.
أنا استطيع.
Eyes on the road.
عيون على الطريق.
There's something I need to tell you.
هناك شيء أريد أن أخبرك به.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
He knows we're investigating the old case.
إنه يعلم أننا نحقق في القضية القديمة.
How did he know?
كيف عرف؟
It's my fault.
إنه خطئي.
I wasn't careful enough.
لم أكن حذرا بما فيه الكفاية.
What does he know?
ماذا يعرف؟
He knows everything we've found out.
إنه يعرف كل ما اكتشفناه.
But here's what I think.
ولكن هذا ما أعتقده.
Maybe it's good that we tell him.
ربما من الجيد أن نقول له.
Some things are much easier for the Intelligence Department
بعض الأمور أسهل بكثير بالنسبة لقسم الاستخبارات
to investigate than for us.
للتحقيق من أجلنا.
It can also help
ويمكن أن يساعد أيضا
clarify things sooner.
توضيح الأمور في وقت أقرب.
But I never expected him to come to the police station.
ولكنني لم أتوقع أبدًا أن يأتي إلى مركز الشرطة.
I didn't tell him about the fire at the abandoned factory.
لم أخبره عن الحريق في المصنع المهجور.
[Ruyi Steamed Buns Shop]
[متجر كعك رويي المطهو ​​على البخار]
Okay, take care.
حسنًا، اعتني بنفسك.
Steamed buns! Hot steamed buns!
كعكات مطهوة على البخار! كعكات مطهوة على البخار ساخنة!
You two,
انتما الاثنان
what would you like to eat?
ماذا تحب أن تأكل؟
I'm Guan Cen, an inspector from the Police Station.
أنا جوان سين، مفتش من مركز الشرطة.
Officer,
ضابط،
we haven't done anything illegal.
لم نفعل أي شيء غير قانوني.
Besides,
بجانب،
this isn't shady business.
هذا ليس عملاً مشبوهاً.
And our prices
وأسعارنا
are already very low.
منخفضة جدًا بالفعل.
Madam, don't panic.
سيدتي، لا داعي للذعر.
We're here for Tao Fan.
نحن هنا من أجل تاو فان.
We want to talk to her.
نريد أن نتحدث معها.
What about her?
ماذا عنها؟
What did she do?
ماذا فعلت؟
She's very well-behaved.
إنها حسنة السلوك للغاية.
She always helps me in the kitchen.
إنها تساعدني دائمًا في المطبخ.
She rarely goes out.
نادرا ما تخرج.
You must have the wrong person.
لابد وأنك مع الشخص الخطأ.
We want to ask her
نريد أن نسألها
about her classmates.
عن زملائها في الفصل.
Is she in the shop now?
هل هي في المحل الآن؟
Tao Fan!
تاو فان!
Madam,
سيدتي،
has Tao Fan been helping at the shop
هل كان تاو فان يساعد في المتجر؟
since she graduated from high school?
منذ تخرجها من المدرسة الثانوية؟
She originally
هي في الأصل
planned to go to college.
خططت للذهاب إلى الكلية.
For some reason,
لسبب ما،
she gave up after finishing high school.
استسلمت بعد الانتهاء من المدرسة الثانوية.
But maybe giving up was for the best.
ولكن ربما كان الاستسلام هو الأفضل.
A family like ours
عائلة مثل عائلتنا
doesn't have that much money for her education.
ليس لديها الكثير من المال لتعليمها.
Besides, she hasn't been in good health.
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، فهي لم تكن تتمتع بصحة جيدة.
It's better she stays with us so we can look after her.
من الأفضل أن تبقى معنا حتى نتمكن من الاعتناء بها.
A family like ours doesn't ask for much.
عائلة مثل عائلتنا لا تطلب الكثير.
We only want
نحن نريد فقط
to live a simple life and stay healthy.
لعيش حياة بسيطة والبقاء بصحة جيدة.
What kind of work does she usually do in the shop?
ما هو نوع العمل الذي تقوم به عادةً في المتجر؟
She does all sorts of odd jobs here.
إنها تقوم بجميع أنواع الأعمال الغريبة هنا.
She was just helping her father wash dishes in the kitchen.
لقد كانت تساعد والدها في غسل الأطباق في المطبخ.
Her father went to buy groceries.
ذهب والدها لشراء البقالة.
As for her,
أما بالنسبة لها،
she's afraid of getting her own shoes wet,
إنها تخاف من أن تبتل حذائها،
so she always likes to wear her father's rain boots.
لذلك فهي تحب دائمًا ارتداء أحذية المطر الخاصة بوالدها.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Madam.
سيدتي.
I might need to take those rain boots.
ربما أحتاج إلى أخذ أحذية المطر تلك.
Wait a moment.
انتظر لحظة.
Dong.
دونغ.
These shoes were brought back by Lu Yizhen.
تم جلب هذه الأحذية من قبل لو يي تشن.
See if we can find any clues.
دعونا نرى ما إذا كان بوسعنا العثور على أي أدلة.
These shoes belong to Tao Fan.
هذه الأحذية تعود إلى تاو فان.
She's been taken by Guan Cen and Lu Yizhen
لقد تم أخذها بواسطة Guan Cen وLu Yizhen
for questioning.
للاستفسار.
Take a look.
خذ نظرة.